(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-04T22:38:07.979402",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
In-Stock Merch: Light Stick, T-Shirt
Made-To-Order Merch: Random Button Badge
Made-To-Order Merch: Acrylic Stand Coaster
Made-To-Order Merch: Tapestry, Acrylic Panel, Mug
Made-To-Order Merch: Happi
hololive English 3rd Concert "ALL FOR ONE" Fan Messages
On the Run! hololive English -Advent- 2nd Anniversary Live
ZOM-RAID TIME
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment for the start.
Attention For Visitors
In-Stock Merch: Essentials Pack
In-Stock Merch
Made-to-Order Merch: Random Button Badge
Made-to-Order Merch: Acrylic Stand Coaster
Made-to-Order Merch: Tapestry, Acrylic Panel, Mug
Made-to-Order Merch: Happi
hololive English 3rd Concert: ALL FOR ONE Fan Messages
On the Run! hololive English -Advent- 2nd Anniversary Live
It's Ollie's holoplus ZOM-RAID TIME
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment.
Attention For Visitors
In-Stock Merch: Essentials Pack
In-Stock Merch
【現地・通販グッズ】ペンライト、Tシャツ
[In-Stock Merch] Light Stick, T-Shirt
【受注販売グッズ】ランダム缶バッジ
[Made-to-Order Merch] Random Button Badge
【受注販売グッズ】アクリルスタンドコースター
[Made-to-Order Merch] Acrylic Stand Coaster
【受注販売グッズ】タペストリー、アクリルパネル、マグカップ
[Made-to-Order Merch] Tapestry, Acrylic Panel, Mug
【受注販売グッズ】ハッピ
[Made-to-Order Merch] Happi
【応援メッセージ】ファンからのメッセージ紹介
[Fan Support Messages]
hololive English -Advent- 2nd Anniversary Live "On the Run!"
holoplus「ZOM-RAID TIME」with クレイジー・オリー
holoplus "ZOM-RAID TIME" with Kureiji Ollie
【まもなく開演】hololive English 3rd Concert "ALL FOR ONE"
[Starting Soon] hololive English 3rd Concert "ALL FOR ONE"
【注意事項】演出におけるフラッシュライトへの注意 / 声出し大歓迎
[Attention] Please be aware of flashing lights / Loud cheering is allowed
【現地・通販グッズ】エッセンシャルパック
[In-Stock Merch] Essentials Pack
ALL FOR ONE × HYTE コラボグッズ
ALL FOR ONE x HYTE Collaboration Merch
WAH! Good Morning, Afternoon, and Evening! It's me, Ina!
I hope everyone is excited for the concert! I know I am!
I've been AmiAmi's ambassador for a full year now,
and it's been so much fun sharing all the great memories and the cool merch with you!
I've been using AmiAmi for a long time, but I still get
excited every time I spot something WAHnderful on AmiAmi
- it's like finding treasure!
Whenever you find cute merch of your oshi on AmiAmi,
be sure to let us know, okay?
Let's give AmiAmi a big thank you for everything they've done this year!
Everyone say, Thank you AmiAmi!
Anyways, let's make more amazing memories tonight!
Make sure to cheer with everything you've got, okay?
WAH!
[グッズ情報] 在庫販売グッズ
[Merchandise] In-Stock Merch
[グッズ情報] 受注販売：ランダム缶バッジ
[Merchandise] Made-to-Order: Random Button Badge
[グッズ情報] 受注販売：アクリルスタンドコースター
[Merchandise] Made-to-Order: Acrylic Stand Coaster
[グッズ情報] 受注販売：タペストリー、アクリルパネル、マグカップ
[Merchandise] Made-to-Order: Tapestry, Acrylic Panel, Mug
[グッズ情報] 受注販売：ハッピ
[Merchandise] Made-to-Order: Happi
[ファンメッセージ]
[Fan Messages]
[告知] hololive English -Advent- 2nd Anniversary Live 「On the Run!」
[Info] hololive English -Advent- 2nd Anniversary Live "On the Run!"
[告知] ホロプラス：Ollieの「ZOM-RAID TIME」
[Info] holoplus: Ollie's "ZOM-RAID TIME"
[告知] 開演までしばらくお待ちください。
[Info] The concert will be starting soon. Please wait.
[注意事項] 演出中のフラッシュライトにご注意ください。声出し応援は可能です。
[Attention] Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
[グッズ情報] 在庫販売：エッセンシャルパック
[Merchandise] In-Stock Merch: Essentials Pack
In-Stock Merch
Made-To-Order Merch
Random Button Badge
Acrylic Stand Coaster
Tapestry, Acrylic Panel, Mug
Happi
hololive English 3rd Concert
ALL FOR ONE
Let's go! Let's go!
hololive English 3rd Concert
ALL FOR ONE
Holo-live! Holo-live!
hololive English 3rd Concert
ALL FOR ONE
hololive English -ALL FOR ONE-
hololive English 3rd Concert -ALL FOR ONE-
Mori Calliope
MYTH
Mori Calliope / Takanashi Kiara / Ninomae Ina'nis
Hakos Baelz
PROMISE
IRyS / Ouro Kronii / Hakos Baelz
Shiori Novella
Nerissa Ravencroft
Mococo Abyssgard
ADVENT
Shiori Novella / Koseki Bijou / Nerissa Ravencroft / Fuwawa Abyssgard / Mococo Abyssgard
Gigi Murin
JUSTICE
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame / Gigi Murin / Cecilia Immergreen / Raora Panthera
hololive English 3rd Concert ALL FOR ONE
Yeah
Rise up
Come closer now
Bring it on
Get down right now
Fighter
Fearless
Step it up, step it up now
We got the power, start the fire
burning up inside our soul
Nothing brings us down
no matter what, we're gonna break, break through
Next step, gotta keep going on and on
and on we go, crashing into the dawn
We're gonna break the rules
nobody can do what we can do
Get up, get up, go break out the rules now
Move into the groove, keep it extra cool
No ordinary girl, let 'em know we're in control
Yo, back it up, break it down, let's go
Louder, louder to the beat
Fly higher, higher to the sky
Yeah, here we go, grab it, no time to waste
Listen to your heart, leave your mind behind
Out of the reality, I heard a whisper
calling me...
I see it now, we found ourselves
bound to be... yeah!
Hey, start again! We're never gonna stop!
輝く星 響き合わせて
Shining stars, resonating together
Hey, start again! Let go and let it flow!
Let it out, here we go, supernatural feeling
無限に広がるステージを駆け抜けてSing along
Running through the infinitely expanding stage, sing along
No more limits, taking off, keep it going on and on!
Shout out loud and reach out to the moon, not afraid, there's nothing left to lose
Oh, start something more, yes, turn it up into the...
...new world! We are unbreakable now!
We know what's going on, let's take it real slow from head to toe
Ready or not, turn it up to the beat
Burn, burn, burning, burning...
Focus on us, step by step, pump it up
to the limit till the end, yeah, yeah!
Out of the reality, I heard a whisper
calling me...
I see it now, we found ourselves
bound to be... yeah!
Hey, start again! We're never gonna stop!
輝く星 響き合わせて
Shining stars, resonating together
Hey, start again! Let go and let it flow!
Let it out, here we go, supernatural feeling
Hold back, you can't block, get in the way of us no more!
No stop, we're right at the revolutionary! Hey yo, come on, get up, get up!
Never gonna lose, we're invincible now, going higher and higher, the energy grows
Running under control, here we go, keep it up, we're counting down!
Go louder, go louder, go louder, go louder
Go louder, go louder, go louder now!
This is us, we're ruling the world!
Hey, start again! We're never gonna stop!
輝く星 響き合わせて
Shining stars, resonating together
Hey, start again! Let go and let it flow!
Let it out, here we go, supernatural feeling
無限に広がるステージを駆け抜けてSing along
Running through the infinitely expanding stage, sing along
No more limits, taking off, keep it going on and on!
Shout out loud and reach out to the moon, not afraid, there's nothing left to lose
Oh, start something more, yes, turn it up into the...
...new world!
We are unbreakable, we are unbreakable now!
私のもの そう私のもの
It's mine, yes, it's mine...
千の黄金 数百年の財宝
A thousand gold pieces, hundreds of years of treasure...
この船に眠る
...resting inside this ship.
Are you ready to rock?
One, two, three, four!
古びた伝説は
The old legend...
呪われた幽霊船に
...on the cursed ghost ship...
続く夜の潮路
...following the night tide.
そこに富が遺る
There, the wealth remains.
海賊の夢があるのなら
If you have a pirate's dream...
去らうしかないでしょう
There is no choice but to sweep it away
無謀な火を我が身に宿すよ
I harbor a reckless fire within myself
命もろとも荒海に返してやろう
I'll return you to the rough seas, along with your life
止まない雨の弾丸で
With bullets of endless rain
穿つほどにこの身に焦がす
Burning myself to the point of piercing through
生命の炎が燃えとろけ
The flame of life melts and burns
色彩さらん 宝石的なのなら
If it's jewel-like, sweeping away the colors...
私のもの そう私のもの
It's mine, yes, it's mine
奪ってみせるよ 命の証を
I'll show you I can seize the proof of life
あなたの求める全てを
Everything that you desire
輝かせてみせるから
Because I will make it shine
触れてみろ 女神が紡ぐなら
Try and touch it, if a goddess spins it
泡沫と共に沈め
Sink along with the bubbles
美しきストーリー作り出す
Creating a beautiful story
極上の海賊の秘宝
The finest pirate treasure
手に入れる 風は笑う
I will obtain it, as the wind laughs
魔術の禁忌修業
The forbidden study of magic
七つの海を我が手に
The seven seas in my hands
だから 模範の徒も
Therefore, even the model disciples...
おとりと目を狙う
Aiming for the decoy and the eyes
愚か者に鉄槌下す
I will strike down the fools with a hammer
騒がしき侵入者を
The noisy intruders...
この身に宿る この怒りの炎で
With this flame of anger dwelling in my body
影の底で 死に追いやる 絶望の渦
At the bottom of the shadows, driving them to death in a whirlpool of despair
まるで 二人の閉じた箱
Just like a closed box for the two of us
諦めちゃうの？ 諦めちゃうの？
Are you going to give up? Are you going to give up?
諦めちゃったら 逃げられるのに まだ戦ってる
Even though you could escape if you gave up, you're still fighting
よっぽどタフだから
Because you are incredibly tough
私のもの そう私のもの
It's mine, yes, it's mine
自分自身を信じ込ませて スマート
Convincing yourself of it, so smart
縛り付けてたって気づいた
I realized I was being tied down
魔法の手口 永久の回帰
A magical trick, an eternal recurrence
目を見開いて あなたの悪夢から
Open your eyes wide, and from your nightmare...
連れ出す 危機を抜けよ
I will lead you out, escape the crisis!
スタートして
Start!
私のもの まだ私のもの
It's mine, it's still mine
勝負の時は 満ち果てたとしても
Even if the time of battle is completely spent
枯れない魂までは
Even down to our unwithering souls
何百光年 永遠 of 美貌を
Hundreds of light-years, eternal beauty...
どんな幻像とも戦ってきたでしょう
We must have fought against any illusion, right?
負けず劣らず 戦った
We fought, neither yielding to the other
愛おしき 余計に 覚悟決めて
With more resolve than necessary for what we love
異世界を渡ってきた船
The ship that crossed over from another world
今度は私が 残していく
This time, I'll be the one to leave you behind
神はもういない
God is no longer here
さらば
Farewell
Hello, New York!
Are you ready to put your hands up?
I want to see all your hands! Let's go!
Put your hands up!
Put your, put your hands up!
Let's go!
Put your hands up! Put your, put your hands up!
実際の感情は No Think! 気づかないふり...?
No need to think about real feelings, are you pretending not to notice?
絶対的な虚実と心中 そうやって減っていくアンチ
The absolute truth and your own heart? And the safety zone is shrinking,
傷の切り売り もろく叫ぶ、醜態
selling wounds piece by piece, so you let out a feeble and shameful cry for help!
そんなあなたにおすすめ！最高級の逃避行
Well I've got a recommendation for you like that! The grandest escape!
やがて、甘い罠に釣られたものから救われる？
Even if you fall into a sweet trap, you can be saved everyday!
もはや正気の沙汰ではやっていけないこの街じゃ
Now we can't live sanely in this world anymore.
あえて知らん顔で身を任せるのが最適カイ？
Is surrendering yourself solution number one?
言葉で飾った花束も心を奪えば、本物（ほんもの）か？
If a bouquet dressed up with words can steal one's heart, are they real?
全てが染まっていくような
To a colorful world tainted with words,
事象にご招待
I'll give you an invitation,
さらば！
farewell!
Put your hands up!
Put your, put your hands up!
Everybody!
Put your hands up! Put your, put your hands up!
こんな時代に阿修羅えた 見得のれの脆弱性
You're tailor-made for this era, with an appearance of vulnerability!
本当の芝居でだまされる やたらとうるさい心臓の鼓動
Fooled by this truthful acting, your heart beats so very loudly!
賛否はとうに無いナッティン 擦り減る耐久性
Your extra lives are quickly being lost! Your durability worn away!
目の前の事象をかわしつつ生きるので精一杯
Dodging matters right in front of you, you got your hands full of living!
ちっちゃい ちっちゃい ちっちゃい 器
You're small, you're small, you're small-minded!
おーわっ おーわっ おーわっ あい
Oh-wah, oh-wah, oh-wah, eye,
気分ははい ことっ たん
feeling high, click-clack!
おーわっ おーわっ おーわっ あい
Oh-wah, oh-wah, oh-wah, eye,
あいるもおーあい ことっ ぱん
I'm also doing OAI click-clack.
繋がってんだ 記録なんだ
We're connected, it's recorded,
DNA メンツ メンツ
DNA, our face, our pride,
面目 紡いだ 犬 猿 雉 猫
honor spun by dog, monkey, pheasant, and cat.
お商売だ 働いてんだ 連勤なんだ
It's business, I'm working consecutive shifts,
休み無し毎日が キツ キツ キツ の夜
every day without a break is so tight, tight, tight...
あー
Ah!
乱痴気騒ぎ 燦々と照らした信号
A wild party, a signal shining brightly,
人類滅亡させちゃう AI 暴走
an out-of-control AI that will destroy humanity.
あーもう 惨死 惨死 警告信号
Ah, tragic death, tragic death, a warning signal,
指、指まで ワンツースリーで だんだんだんさ
even to our fingers, one, two, three, step by step.
だん さー
Step, step...
Okay New York!
You're gonna hate me for saying this...
Let's go vintage!
Oh my god, oh my life
ようやく死に物狂いで辿り着いた
Finally arrived after fighting tooth and nail,
まぐれだね 抜け殻精神で
it's a fluke, with a shell of a spirit,
ほれ、ほれ、ほれ、ほれ...
look, look, look...
We're just getting started so give me your energy!
Put your hands up! Up! Put your, put your hands up!
ドブネズミも ほら
Even a sewer rat, look,
転げ回るだろな
would roll around, right?
そう、ワン、ワン、ワン、ワン、ワン、ワン、ワン
Just like that, woof, woof, woof, woof, woof, woof, woof!
脳内全開だ やっぱ ぽいじゃん ぽいじゃん ぽい
My brain is fully open, it's definitely "ish", "ish", "ish"!
手をつないで踊れば まあ、愛、愛、愛
If we hold hands and dance, well, it's love, love, love!
散々ふりまいて どうしたの？ 奪ったの？
Scattering it around in abundance, what's wrong? Did you steal it?
ほら、そうやって ちっちゃい ちっちゃい ちっちゃい 器
Look, just like that, you're small, you're small, you're small-minded!
おーわっ おーわっ おーわっ あい
Oh-wah, oh-wah, oh-wah, eye,
気分ははい ことっ たん
feeling high, click-clack!
おーわっ おーわっ おーわっ あい
Oh-wah, oh-wah, oh-wah, eye,
あいるもおーあい ことっ ぱん
I'm also doing OAI click-clack.
Put your hands up! Up! Put your, put your hands up!
Takanashi Kiara
IRyS
New York!
Are you ready for some spice?
Oh no
Fell into the abyss unknown
Left me bleeding, heartless, all alone, yeah
No control, yeah
Don't you dare apologize
Turn my back and felt a cold knife
Listen up, 'cause here's some advice
You're out of time, way out of line
It's taking over like a renegade
Eye for an eye, I'll make you cry
Tearing it down, do just what I wanna
Keep calling me a sinner (know you think so)
Chimeri-eri-eria (got me twisted)
Chimeri-eri-eria (such a misfit)
Taking the crown, now you're calling me king
You gonna hear 'em all sing (now sing it)
Chimeri-eri-eria (louder like that)
Chimeri-eri-eria (make 'em all "ah")
Don't back it up, don't back it up, keep that aim
I got thoughts that will drive you insane
Come over if you like, we'll have a lot of fun
But I got a lot of bite
I do what I want, make sure you don't forget it
An army on my back, say I'm sick, I'm just sadistic
Not living in a lie, pariah in the light
I wanna see the way you bleed
It's taking over like a renegade
Eye for an eye, I'll make you cry
Tearing it down, do just what I wanna
Keep calling me a sinner (know you think so)
Chimeri-eri-eria (got me twisted)
Chimeri-eri-eria (such a misfit)
Taking the crown, now you're calling me king
You gonna hear 'em all sing (now sing it)
Chimeri-eri-eria (louder like that)
Chimeri-eri-eria (make 'em all "ah")
I want it all, so gimme some more
Flames burnt me up down into my core
Oh, you wished I'd stay down, but then I just rise
You're not my enemy
Baby, you're dead to me
Hear my voices screaming out loud, no doubt, yeah
La-la-la-la-la-la
M-E-R-M-A-I-D
Chimera
Go!
Tearing it down, do just what I wanna
Keep calling me a sinner
Chimera, chimera
Taking the crown, now you're calling me king
You gonna hear 'em all sing
Chimera, chimera
La-la-la-la-la-la, chimera
Wait, no one is cheering!
Oh, Kiara!
You're cheating on RyS?!
Well, we did it, you know.
Oh, yeah, that's...
Wait, we didn't do anything wrong!
We're not... we're not doing anything wrong!
No, no, no, we were just hugging as friends!
It was just "te-te"! "Te-te"! Yes, "te-te".
KiaraRyS! And IRyS!
Okay, let's introduce ourselves, yeah? Yes.
You... start with the cheater... Oh, no!
No! No! I am not a cheater!
Okay... Go ahead! Go ahead!
Kiki-riki!
Hi, I wish I was someone else right now,
but I'm Takanashi Kiara from hololive English -Myth-! Yay!
And you? Oh! Hi RyS!
It's IRyS from hololive English Promise! Can I get a "Hi RyS"?
Hi RyS! Let's go!
We just performed a really high performance...
yes... of Chimera!
Chimera!
This is not my first time performing with you on your song.
Yeah, they put us together a lot these days.
I know, we're trends! We're trends!
The KiaraRyS... The KiaraRyS is a trend!
Yeah!
I'm sure they are. They can't get enough of us, right?
No, of course they can't! That's why we're here now, too.
We're spice. We're sexy.
Oh, yes, we are! Yes, we are! Of course we are.
Well, well, you know, it's the first time seeing us.
That's right, which means...
Oh...
we're going to do the sad news, right? Yes.
But I want to deliver the sad news!
It's our first time, so I want to do it too!
But I want to do it!
Well, in that case, we battle it out!
We're battling it out? In front of all these people?
Yeah, there's no problem. They are going to cheer for us.
Well, we think of battles, what do we think of?
I think, like recently, a lot of the EN members have been doing arm wrestling.
And I am very well-known for being a noodle arm person. What about you?
I am very strong! Oh!
Everyone knows that IRyS is very strong. Yeah, sure.
Well, you know, I usually am left-handed, but I will use my right hand to give you a chance, okay?
Thank you, Senpai. Okay, okay, okay.
I will take that challenge right now! Let's go!
Okay, come here. Come here, come here.
Count us down! Three, two, one, go!
I'm gonna win! Yes!
I won! Yes! I defeated her!
Non-dominant arm!
But that was my right hand, though. My left hand is my dominant arm.
So that wasn't completely fair.
Let's do another game. Another game?! Yes!
I mean, yeah, that's true, it wasn't fair. In that case, what do you have in mind?
There's this game called, like, blue light... red light. Not blue light. That's red light, green light.
Red light, green light. Okay.
Okay, then you perhaps stand on that side, and I will go towards you. Okay.
Alright, alright. Got you.
Okay, then I... I can win this! I will get you. I will get you, okay?
Okay. Red light! Oh, green light!
Oh, sorry. We're starting, we're starting. Okay, okay.
Red light!
Green light! Red light, green light!
Red light! Green light!
Red light, green light, red light!
No, my butt! Not my butt!
Okay! Yay!
But that means it's a draw. A draw? Which means...
We get to say it together!
Ah...!
Teary ending.
A teary ending.
It's not like this was scripted or anything. I swear I actually...
No, no, no, no!
The only thing that was scripted was our entrance.
Oh, yeah, that. Okay.
Then...
Let's do it!
Let's do this, okay.
Everybody watching on YouTube...
Mhm.
...are you aware
...that if you don't have a ticket, you might not be able to
...watch any more of this?!
What?!
Yes, guys!
This is the last of the free part on YouTube!
If you want to watch more, you have to buy the streaming tickets!
They're available in the description and the official website!
Probably down there, yeah. You can go get the streaming ticket.
Yeah, you would be crying like me until you buy them!
Yes!
Do what she says, I recommend it.
Also if you buy them, you'll be happy and you'll be able to watch the rest of the concert!
Yay!
Yes, yes, yes! They're saying it too!
They are!
Buy it! Buy it!
Besides that, one more thing.
Mhm.
Now that you've got your tickets and you're ready to take even more screenshots...
...make sure to share them and your thoughts on social media using the hashtag...
#holoAllforOne! Yes!
Yes! So...
Speaking of All for One, I think it's time for us to...
...you know, say the thing.
Yeah, the thing. You guys are all aware by now, right?
But because of yesterday, it's called All for One. We say it together.
We say it together, yeah? All of us.
All of us. お願いします。
All of us. We're counting on you.
Are you in or what? Okay.
All for One.
All for One. Okay, okay.
Ready? Okay. Three, two, one...
All for One!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Official Hashtag #holoAllforOne
[The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!]
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Official Hashtag #holoAllforOne
[The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!]
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Official Hashtag #holoAllforOne
[The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!]
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free-to-watch portion has ended! Thank you for watching!